mambosprouts.com 2007-12-04

# Mambo Sprouts Privacy Policy

## MAMBO SPROUTS PRIVACY POLICY 

## A. DISCLAIMER

This site does not provide any medical or health care advice. Consult your physician or other qualified health care provider for advice regarding medical and health conditions. Do not attempt to self-diagnose or treat any medical condition based on any information contained in this site.

##  *NEW*Mambo Sprouts Privacy Statement  

(Last updated: April 29,2004)

Mambo Sprouts is committed to protecting your privacy. This Mambo Sprouts Privacy Statement applies to data collection and usage on this site; it does not apply to other online or offline partner sites. Please read the Mambo Sprouts Privacy Statement below.

Mambo Sprouts is a general audience web site. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Statement. Any child under the age or 13 must get their parent of guardians permission prior to submitting any personal information or accessing this site.

## Collection of your Personal Information

Mambo Sprouts collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, home address, first name, last name, telephone number, city, state and zip code. Mambo Sprouts will store all of the information you provide securely. 

## Use of your Personal Information 

Mambo Sprouts uses your personal information to operate Mambo Sprouts and deliver the information and services you have requested. 

Mambo Sprouts may also use your personal information to inform you of other products or services through special coupon and product offers available from Mambo Sprouts and/or its affiliates, unless you specifically elect not to receive these offers. Mambo Sprouts may also contact you via surveys to conduct market research and to better service our customers.

Mambo Sprouts **DOES NOT** sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Mambo Sprouts may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is NOT transferred to the third party. Mambo Sprouts occasionally exchanges its customer list with other like minded publications that it feels may be of interest.

## Control of your Personal Information

Mambo Sprouts offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may opt out of receiving emails by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive. You may also stop all emails or mailings by sending a letter to the address stated below in the contact section or by calling the number below.

## Enforcement of this Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, please first contact Mambo Sprouts via e-mail at [info@mambosprouts.com](mailto:info@mambosprouts.com).

## Changes to this Statement

Mambo Sprouts will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. When Mambo Sprouts posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" below the Privacy Statement title on this page. Mambo Sprouts encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

## Contact Information

Mambo Sprouts welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you believe that Mambo Sprouts has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Mambo Sprouts by telephone, e-mail, or postal mail.

856-833-1933
